# ROMAN JASIEK

# WEB DEVELOPER



Web developer with 20 years of experience in sales, 10+ years experience as WordPress enthusiast and writer/blogger who will soon graduate a 1-year intensive remote training in Full Stack Web Development (MERN Stack).

I am looking for a position, where I can bring in all my experiences, where I can challenge myself and deliver solution oriented approaches. I always have maximum customer satisfaction in mind and I implement the STAR method.

#### **CONTACT**

**ADDRESS** 

9

Schillerstr. 47, 39108 Magdeburg

PHONE

+49 - 172 - 4563446

**EMAIL** 

romanjasiek@me.com

WEBSITE / PORTFOLIO

romanjasiek.de

SOCIAL MEDIA

linkedin.com/in/romanjasiek/

## **EDUCATION**

# Full Stack Web Development (MERN Stack)

Digital Career Institute gGmbH | 2021/02 - 2022/01

- Accomplishing a one-year-full-time training including technologies from MERN stack
- Completing a couple of small projects to practice programming skills
- Completing several additional courses on platforms like Udemy to learn and practice more

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Team Lead

Amazon Logistik Suelzetal GmbH | 2020

 Workflow controller between different departments in the outbound area of a major logistics center

#### District Manager

Wüstenrot Bausparkasse AG | 2019 - 2020

- Self-employed sales representative according to §84 HGB
- Sale of insurance and financial products

# **Customer Service Representative**

Targobank AG | 2019

 Telephone acquisition of new customers, advising existing customers on topics related to the digital transformation of the bank

#### **Apple Master & Specialist Consultant**

Saturn Electro Handelsges. mbH | 2012 - 2018

- Specialist consultant in the Computer Hardware & Accessories department
- Brand ambassador for Apple Inc.

# ROMAN JASIEK

# WEB DEVELOPER





### **SKILLS**

HTML5

CSS3 / Sass /SCSS

Bootstrap / Tailwind CSS

JavaScript (ES5/ES6)

MongoDB / Firebase

**Express** 

React.js / Next.js / Node.js

Git/GitHub

WordPress

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Lightroom

Agile Software Development

Deutsch (native speaker)

English (fluent)

# **PORTFOLIO**

#### Personal Portfolio

HTML5, CSS3, Sass, JS, React

romanjasiek.de

#### **Music Evangelists**

Wordpress

musicevangelists.com

#### **Coding Tunes**

React, CSS, Sass

romanjasiek.github.io/vaguemusic-player

#### **MERN Social Network**

MongoDB, Express, React, Node

github.com/romanjasiek/thesoci alnetwork-client

github.com/romanjasiek/thesoci

alnetwork-server

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Sales Representative**

GRAVIS Computervertriebsges. mbH | 2011 - 2012

- Sales advisor for Apple hardware and software of all kinds
- Software support and tutoring, minor hardware repairs

#### **Bookseller & IT Support**

Thalia Bücher GmbH | 2007 - 2011

- Sale of books, management of own merchandise groups (purchase, returns, presentation of products)
- Germany-wide assistance with the transition of the stores to an SAP-based ERP system

## Store Manager (Parental leave replacement)

Weltbild Plus Medien Vertriebs GmbH & Co.KG | 2005 - 2006

- Sales operations
- Personnel planning, applicant selection, and conducting recruitment interviews
- Planning and realization of marketing activities

#### Sales Representative

PowerBeam! e.K. | 2005 - 2005

# **Production Helper**

ZAG Zeitarbeits-Gesellschaft GmbH | 2004 - 2004

#### **Bookseller**

Thalia Bücher GmbH | 2002 - 2002

# **Bookseller Apprenticeship**

Thalia Bücher GmbH | 1999 - 2002